<Calendar>
	<Day>
		<Date>12 February 2016</Date>
		<Events>
			<Event>
				<Name>Parkour Club</Name>
				<Category>Audacity College</Category>
				<Text>
					As usual, the Audacity College Parkour Club will be holding its weekly meeting on Friday. For those who are not aware, parkour is an atheletic activity that consists mainly of jumping on things. And also off of things. And jumping from one thing to another thing. Sometimes, some of these things are the ground. Parkour is sometimes called 'urban gymnastics', but that name is discouraged because it conjures the image of a bunch of assholes in backwards baseball caps listening to Coldplay, which is the Audacity College Steller School of Business, not the Parkour Club. &lt;/p&gt;
					All who are intrested in learning parkour are welcome to attend. The bus leaves at 8:45 PM from Ireland.
				</Text>
			</Event>
			<Event>
				<Name>Thursday Beethoven Night</Name>
				<Category>Community</Category>
				<Text>
					Due to a clerical error, the Thursday Beethoven Night at the town hall will take place on Friday. It will also take place at the Rockettopia Senior Center lobby - not the Town Hall - at 1 AM and will feature gangster rap instead of Beethoven. The Rockettopia town council apologizes for the errors.
				</Text>
			</Event>
		</Events>
	</Day>
	<Day>
		<Date>13 February 2016</Date>
		<Events>
			<Event>
				<Name>Trump Rally</Name>
				<Category>Community</Category>
				<Text>
					The Trump for President campaign is holding another rally in the old abandoned warehouse in the industrial park, which is the only building in town that is willing to host them for any sum of money. The entire public is invited to come. Following the events of last month's rally, attendees have been instructed not to wear swastika armbands or do the Hitler salute, even if they mean it as a compliment.
				</Text>
			</Event>
			<Event>
				<Name>ISIS Flag Burning</Name>
				<Category>Community</Category>
				<Text>
					The Rockettopia Council for International Engagement will be holding an ISIS flag burning on the town common at 2:30 PM. They plan to chant "USA! USA!" while burning the terrorist group's flag, as well as effigies of Abu Bakr al-Baghdadi and other ISIS leaders, if such things can be obtained. The RCIE says that the event will make the community feel like they're doing something to help fight the war without having to go through the trouble of actually doing anything meaningful.
				</Text>
			</Event>
		</Events>
	</Day>
	<Day>
		<Date>14 February 2016</Date>
		<Events>
			<Event>
				<Name>Valentine's Day</Name>
				<Category>Secular Holidays</Category>
				<Text>
					Either the most romantic or most unpleasent day of the year, depending on who you are.
				</Text>
			</Event>
			<Event>
				<Name>Barbed-Wire-Eating Event</Name>
				<Category>Audacity College</Category>
				<Text>
					The student council will once again be holding their popular Valentine's Day barbed-wire-eating event. Students without dates for Valentine's Day are invited to show up and be force-fed barbed wire in a vain attempt to briefly distract from the soul-crushing loneliness. Also, free snacks and prizes for whoever eats the most barbed wire! The record is thirty feet. It's a lot of fun!
				</Text>
			</Event>
			<Event>
				<Name>Super-Secret Bankus Hall Orgy</Name>
				<Category>Audacity College</Category>
				<Text>	
					Audacity's Bankus Hall is throwing a super-secret Valentine's Day orgy! No one is supposed to know, which is why I'm writing about it here, where I can be absolutely sure that no one will see it. Some marijuana and alcohol will be provided, but guests are encouraged to bring their own. Cocaine will not be provided, although again, guests are invited to bring their own. &lt;br/&gt;
					Again, you are &lt;b&gt;not supposed to know&lt;/b&gt; about this!
				</Text>
			</Event>
		</Events>
	</Day>
	<Day>
		<Date>15 February 2016</Date>
		<Events>
			<Event>
				<Name>Hat Day</Name>
				<Category>Zohan Middle School</Category>
				<Text>
					Monday is hat day at The Zohan Middle School. Students at The Zohan will, for a $1 donation, be allowed a one-day exemption to the school's 'no hats' rule.
				</Text>
			</Event>
		</Events>
	</Day>
	<Day>
		<Date>16 February 2016</Date>
		<Events>
			<Event>
				<Name>Pants Day</Name>
				<Category>Zohan Middle School</Category>
				<Text>
					Tuesday is Pants Day at The Zohan. For a donation of only $5000, students will be allowed a one-day exemption from the school's 'you have to wear pants' requirement.
				</Text>
			</Event>
			<Event>
				<Name>Mardi Gras</Name>
				<Category>Audacity College</Category>
				<Text>
					A Mardi Gras celebration is being held in the IDX Student Life Center's Fireside lounge. Attendees are expected to bring their own beads to throw at the strippers. Alcohol will not be tolerated, except for Budweiser&amp;reg;, the official sponsorer of Audacity College. 
				</Text>
			</Event>
		</Events>
	</Day>
	<Day>
		<Date>17 February 2016</Date>
		<Events>
			<Event>
				<Name>Wiccan Ash Wednesday</Name>
				<Category>Wiccan Holidays</Category>
				<Text>
					Wiccans &lt;del&gt;avenge&lt;/del&gt; remember two thousand years of persecution by definitely not kidnapping and burning Catholics. If there happen to be any mysterious disappearances of Catholics on Wiccan Ash Wednesday, it is in no way related to Wiccan Ash Wednesday.
				</Text>
			</Event>
		</Events>
	</Day>
	<Day>
		<Date>18 February 2016</Date>
		<Events>
			<Event>
				<Name>Warrent Thursday</Name>
				<Category>Wiccan Holidays</Category>
				<Text>
					The day when Wiccans are taken in for questioning by the police following the events of Wiccan Ash Wednesday.
				</Text>
			</Event>
		</Events>
	</Day>
	<Day>
		<Date>19 February 2016</Date>
		<Events>
			<Event>
				<Name>Release Thursday</Name>
				<Category>Wiccan Holidays</Category>
				<Text>
					The day when Wiccans are released from custody after the chief of police's family develop mysterious swellings that no doctor can explain. The police declare the missing people to be cold cases and everyone tries to forget this whole thing until next year.
				</Text>
			</Event>
		</Events>
	</Day>
	<Day>
		<Date>20 February 2016</Date>
		<Events>
			<Event>
				<Name>Antonin Scalia Memorial Extravaganza</Name>
				<Category>Community</Category>
				<Text>
					A memorial service for the late Supreme Court Justice Antonin Scalia will be held at the abandoned warehouse in the industrial park. Effigies will be provided, but attendees will be expected to bring their own champagne and rotten tomatoes for throwing.
				</Text>
			</Event>
		</Events>
	</Day>
	<Day>
		<Date>21 February 2016</Date>
		<Events>
			<Event>
				<Name>Antonin Scalia Memorial Extravaganza (cont.)</Name>
				<Category>Community</Category>
				<Text>
					The memorial extravaganza for the late Justice Scalia will continue, with male, female, gay and straight strippers paying tribute to Scalia via interpritave dance. Scalia will also be celebrated by public gun-meltings and a drive to register minorities to vote. Again, attendees are encouraged to bring their own alcohol, and while cocaine is technically not allowed, if someone was to bring some the security might look the other way.
				</Text>
			</Event>
			<Event>
				<Name>Jeb Bush Concession Speech</Name>
				<Category>National</Category>
				<Text>
					Hopefully.
				</Text>
			</Event>
		</Events>
	</Day>
	<Day>
		<Date>22 February 2016</Date>
		<Events>
			<Event>
				<Name>Slavoni Troops Arrive in Iraq</Name>
				<Category>World</Category>
				<Text>
					The Slavoni expiditionary force that was sent to fight ISIS last year is scheduled to arrive today. The Rockettopia-Slavonistan Society will celebrate by firing the gun on the tank given to us by Slavonistan, which now gaurds the border with Raiderton.
				</Text>
			</Event>
		</Events>
	</Day>
	<Day>
		<Date>23 February 2016</Date>
	</Day>
	<Day>
		<Date>24 February 2016</Date>
	</Day>
	<Day>
		<Date>25 February 2016</Date>
	</Day>
	<Day>
		<Date>26 February 2016</Date>
		<Events>
			<Event>
				<Name>Active Minds Meeting</Name>
				<Category>Audacity College</Category>
				<Text>Attendance is expected to be very low</Text>
			</Event>
			<Event>
				<Name>Seminar on Repaying Student Loans and Other Superhuman Feats</Name>
				<Category>Audacity College</Category>
				<Text>Mind-reading, telekenesis, levitation, and eating Sodexo burritos will also be covered.</Text>
			</Event>
		</Events>
	</Day>
	<Day>
		<Date>27 February 2016</Date>
	</Day>
	<Day>
		<Date>28 February 2016</Date>
	</Day>
	<Day>
		<Date>29 February 2016</Date>
	</Day>
	<Day>
		<Date>1 March 2016</Date>
		<Events>
			<Event>
				<Name>Super Tuesday</Name>
				<Category>National</Category>
			</Event>
		</Events>
		<Text>
	</Day>
	<Day>
		<Date>2 March 2016</Date>
		<Events>
			<Event>
				<Name>Drinking Binge Wednesday</Name>
				<Category>National</Category>
			</Event>
		</Event>
	</Day>
	<Day>
		<Date>11 April 2016</Date>
		<Events>
			<Event>
				<Name>Start Writing Calendar Again</Name>
				<Category>Local</Category>
			</Event>
		</Events>
	</Day>
</Calendar>